Guide to the Andrea Callard Papers MSS.156
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series II: Andrea Callard Artist Files
  - Subseries C: 1976-1978 40 Lispenard St.
    - 40 Lispenard St. Loft and Environs. 47 color slides on three pages., 1976-1982; cuid22235 (Binder E, Folder a)
    - 40 Lispenard St. Loft and Environs. 35 color slides on three pages., 1976-1982; cuid22236 (Binder E, Folder b)
    - 40 Lispenard St. Loft and Environs. 46 color slides on three pages., 1976-1982; cuid22237 (Binder E, Folder c)
    - 40 Lispenard St. Loft and Environs. 49 color slides on three pages., 1976-1982; cuid22238 (Binder E, Folder d)
    - Canoe trip information packets AC sent to participants., 1977; cuid22239 (Box 2, Folder 147)
    - Canoe trip, black and white contact images, not entire sheets., 1977; cuid22240 (Box 2, Folder 148)
    - Canoe trip texts and Ailanthus tress. Black and white negatives and contact sheets., 1977; cuid22241 (Box 2, Folder 149)
    - Black and white contact sheets and negatives. Ailanthus trees, Jeff Callard and AC's grandparents, 1977; cuid22242 (Box 2, Folder 152)
    - Black and White contact sheet, partial. Ailanthus images, includes Cara Perlman at beach and one of the images used in AC's Ailanthus postcards., 1977; cuid22243 (Box 2, Folder 153)
    - Bat Pamphlet multiples. AC's contribution to Colab's Batman show. Red ink on paper, multiple., 1977; cuid22244 (Box 2, Folder 154)
    - Narrative Drawings, NEA 1976-1977. 12 color slides., cuid22245 (Box 2, Folder 156)
    - Black and white negatives and contact sheet. Fred Krughoff, Cara Perlman, Alan Saret's place., 1977; cuid22246 (Box 2, Folder 157)
    - News and Comment. Black and white photographs used, original altered newspapers and multiple copies., 1977; cuid22247 (Box 2, Folder 158)
    - Transportation incidents postcard samples., 1977; cuid22248 (Box 2, Folder 159)
    - Continental Drift at la Mama. Film by Paula Longendyke. Sets by Andrea Callard and Lizbeth Mararo. Black and white contact sheet and negatives, paper diagram, 60 color slides., 1977; cuid22249 (Box 2, Folder 160)
    - "Love and wrongdoings and retaliation" related to Continental Drift. Index cards wtih text and black and white contact sheet images., 1977-1978; cuid22250 (Box 2, Folder 161)
    - Artists Space: Artists Super 8 Film Exposition. Includes Andrea Callard's Film "Standard Adult Wheelchair", 1977; cuid22251 (Box 2, Folder 162)
    - Color snapshots. "AC Hand photos. Connect to finger print drawings", 1977; cuid22252 (Binder E, Folder e)
    - Ailanthus and Cynthia 1977-1984. 36 color snapsots., cuid22253 (Binder E, Folder f)
    - Black and white negatives. Used for LINE Poster, May 1978, cuid22254 (Box 2, Folder 164A)
    - Black and white contact sheets and negatives from AC's time in the Cummington Community for the Arts, Cummington MA., 1978; cuid22255 (Box 2, Folder 164)
    - Black and white contact sheet and negatives, Cummington, MA. Fred Krughoff, life in the community, the building structure., 1978; cuid22256 (Box 2, Folder 169)
    - Black and white contact sheet and negatives. Cummington, MA: building structure and outdoors., 1978; cuid22257 (Box 2, Folder 170)
    - Black and white contact sheets and negatives. Cummington MA: building interior, 1978; cuid22258 (Box 2, Folder 171)
    - Black and white contact sheet and negatives. Cummington, MA: Kids, outdoors, Andrea Callard and Brick., 1978; cuid22259 (Box 2, Folder 172)
    - Black and white contact sheet. Cummington, MA: building interior., cuid22260 (Box 2, Folder 173)
    - Black and white contact sheet and negatives. Cummington, MA: building interior., 1978; cuid22261 (Box 2, Folder 174)
    - Black and white contact sheet and negatives. Cummington, MA: Fred Krughoff and Andrea Callard in AC's living space., 1978; cuid22262 (Box 2, Folder 175)
    - Black and white contact sheet. Cummington MA: Andrea Callard, shoes, building interior., 1978; cuid22263 (Box 2, Folder 176)
    - Black and white contact sheet and negatives. Cummington, MA: Snowey graveyard, windows., 1978; cuid22264 (Box 2, Folder 177)
    - Black and white contact sheet and negatives. Cummington, MA: windows, Andrea Callard, Fred Krughoff, winter., 1978; cuid22265 (Box 2, Folder 178)
    - Black and white contact sheets and negatives. Cummington, MA: Winter, trees., 1978; cuid22266 (Box 2, Folder 180)
    - Black and white contact sheets and negaties. Andrea Callard and Fred Krughoff, used in mind/heart collages., 1978; cuid22267 (Box 2, Folder 181)
    - Black and white negatives and contact sheets. Customs House, Reese and Carol Williams, Andrea Callard at 40 Lispenard, Wall St. Vicinity, Fred Krugoff, Chuck Callard., 1978; cuid22268 (Box 2, Folder 183)
    - Black and white contact sheets and negatives. Andrea Callard and A. McCall at Ed Chaplin's 14 Harrison St. Loft. Fred Krughoff's loft at 242 Water St., 1978; cuid22269 (Box 2, Folder 184)
    - Six Postcards about Ailanthus Trees. Includes explanation, cards and receipts from friends., 1978; cuid22270 (Box 2, Folder 188)
    - Black and white photographs of drug smuggling paraphenalia on display at the World Trade Center.late 1970s., 1977-1979; cuid22271 (Box 2, Folder 189)
    - Ailanthus drawings and collages. Paper and color photography., 1977-1984; cuid22272 (Box 2, Folder 190)
    - Cynthia moth sketch, part of Ailanthus works., 1977-1984; cuid22273 (Box 2, Folder 191)
    - Black and white Ailanthus photographs, misc., 1977-1984; cuid22274 (Box 2, Folder 192)
    - Ailanthus Landscape, black and white negatives and contact sheets ca. 1978-1982 [Callard's notation]Negatives, three pages., cuid22275 (Binder F, Folder a)
    - Ailanthus Landscape, black and white negatives and contact sheets ca. 1978-1982 [Callard's notation]Negatives, three pages., cuid22276 (Binder F, Folder b)
    - Ailanthus Landscape, black and white negatives and contact sheets ca. 1978-1982 [Callard's notation] Negatives, three pages., cuid22277 (Binder F, Folder c)
    - Ailanthus Landscape, black and white negatives and contact sheets ca. 1978-1982 [Callard's notation]Negatives, three pages., cuid22278 (Binder F, Folder d)
    - Ailanthus Landscape, black and white negatives and contact sheets ca. 1978-1982 [Callard's notation]Negatives, three pages. Contact sheet, one page., cuid22279 (Binder F, Folder e)
    - Ailanthus Landscape, black and white negatives and contact sheets ca. 1978-1982 [Callard's notation]WPA/Citi Wildlife Museum, 1983 negatives and contact sheet., cuid22280 (Binder F, Folder f)
    - Ailanthus Landscape, black and white negatives and contact sheets ca. 1978-1982 [Callard's notation]Contact sheet fragments, seven pages., cuid22281 (Binder F, Folder g)
    - Ailanthus Landscape, black and white negatives and contact sheets ca. 1978-1982 [Callard's notation]Contact sheet and negatives, two pages., cuid22282 (Binder F, Folder h)
    - Ailanthus Landscape, black and white negatives and contact sheets ca. 1978-1982 [Callard's notation]Contact sheet and negatives, two pages., cuid22283 (Binder F, Folder i)
    - Ailanthus Landscape, black and white negatives and contact sheets ca. 1978-1982 [Callard's notation]Contact sheet and negatives, two pages., cuid22284 (Binder F, Folder j)
    - Ailanthus Landscape, black and white negatives and contact sheets ca. 1978-1982 [Callard's notation] Contact sheets, four pages., cuid22285 (Binder F, Folder k)
    - Ailanthus Landscape, black and white negatives and contact sheets ca. 1978-1982 [Callard's notation]Fried eggs and leaves, contact sheet and negatives. Used in "News and Nutrition" work, 1980., cuid22286 (Binder F, Folder l)
    - Ailanthus Landscape, black and white negatives and contact sheets ca. 1978-1982 [Callard's notation]Contact sheets, two pages., cuid22287 (Binder F, Folder m)
    - Ailanthus Landscape, color slides ca. 1978-1982 [Callard's notation]57 color slides on three pages., cuid22288 (Binder F, Folder n)
    - Ailanthus Landscape, color slides ca. 1978-1982 [Callard's notation] 19 color slides on tho pages., cuid22289 (Binder F, Folder o)
    - Ailanthus Landscape, color slides ca. 1978-1982 [Callard's notation] "Ailanthus trees and burned car in field in Staten Is." 47 color slides on three pages., cuid22290 (Binder F, Folder p)
    - Ailanthus Landscape, color slides ca. 1978-1982 [Callard's notation] 32 color slides on three pages., cuid22291 (Binder F, Folder q)
    - Ailanthus Landscape, color slides ca. 1978-1982 [Callard's notation]34 color slides on three pages., cuid22292 (Binder F, Folder r)
    - Ailanthus Landscape, color slides ca. 1978-1982 [Callard's notation] 45 color slides on four pages., cuid22293 (Binder F, Folder s)
  - Subseries D: 1979-1981 40 Lispenard St.
    - "All Animals Need Water to Survive" AC's Contribution to Colab's Animals Living int eh City show. photocopy., 1979; cuid22294 (Box 2, Folder 201)
    - Miscellaneous drawings, 1979; cuid22295 (Box 2, Folder 202)
    - Ailanthus stencil on edit room. two color slides., 1979; cuid22296 (Box 2, Folder 203)
    - Posters advertising Andrea Callard's show "Work from studying Ailanthus" at PS1., 1979; cuid22297 (Box 2, Folder 204)
    - Notes and plans for Seed Machine and Tree Banding, both project part of "Work from Studying Ailanthus" Show at PS1, 1979; cuid22298 (Box 2, Folder 205)
    - Ailanthus project, Seed machine information messages, 1979; cuid22299 (Box 2, Folder 207)
    - Ailanthus: Augmented pamphlet regarding tree planting on streets of Denver, 1979; cuid22300 (Box 2, Folder 208)
    - Custom and Culture II, Announcement., 1979; cuid22301 (Box 2, Folder 209)
    - Custom and Culture II Event program, 1979; cuid22302 (Box 2, Folder 210)
    - Description of Andrea Callard's Custom and Culture II piece., 1979; cuid22303 (Box 2, Folder 212)
    - Sketched floorplan of Customs House, 1979; cuid22304 (Box 2, Folder 213)
    - Ten color slides from AC's Custom and Culture II work., 1979; cuid22305 (Box 2, Folder 214)
    - "Custom Photo Combinations" Custom and Culture II slide show images, color copies., 1979; cuid22306 (Box 2, Folder 215)
    - Custom and Culture II: Press, 1979; cuid22307 (Box 2, Folder 217)
    - Custom and Culture II: Black and white negatives and contact sheeet. Images of stairs, windows, lighting, ornaments, eagle., 1979; cuid22308 (Box 2, Folder 218)
    - Custom and Culture II: Black and white negatives and contact sheets. Images of light fixtures, floors, drawers, windows., 1979; cuid22309 (Box 2, Folder 220)
    - Custom and Culture II: Black and white negatives and contact sheets. Images of building exteriors, statues., 1979; cuid22310 (Box 2, Folder 221)
    - Custom and Culture II: Black and white negatives and contact sheets. Images of archways and windows., 1979; cuid22311 (Box 2, Folder 222)
    - Custom and Culture II: Black and White negatives and contact sheets. Images of windows and stairs., 1979; cuid22312 (Box 2, Folder 223)
    - Custom and Culture II: Black and White negatives and contact sheets. Images of entry area, trash cans, exterior building ornaments., 1979; cuid22313 (Box 2, Folder 224)
    - Custom and Culture II: Black and white negatives and contact sheets. Images of exhibit, fountain, trash., 1979; cuid22314 (Box 2, Folder 225)
    - Custom and Culture II: Black and white negatives and contact sheets. Images of ornamentation, baerial images of building exterior, doorways., 1979; cuid22315 (Box 2, Folder 226)
    - Custom and Culture II: Black and white negatives and contact sheet. Images of exhibit and doors., 1979; cuid22316 (Box 2, Folder 227)
    - Custom and Culture II: Black and white negatives. Image of building exteriors, area surrounding customs house. See folder 228 for corresponding contact sheets., 1979; cuid22317 (Box 2, Folder 229)
    - Custom and Culture II: Black and white negatives. Images of windows, doors, mismatched contact sheet fragment of ironwork., 1979; cuid22318 (Box 2, Folder 230)
    - Custom and Culture II: black and white negatives and contact sheet. Images of sinks, drawers, counters., 1979; cuid22319 (Box 2, Folder 231)
    - Custom and Culture II: black and white negatives and contact sheet. Images of building exterior, Jim Vincent at Andrea Callard's home., 1979; cuid22320 (Box 2, Folder 232)
    - Custom and Culture II: black and white contact sheet and negatives. Images of stairs, brickwork, Andrea Callard and Jim Vincent., 1979; cuid22321 (Box 2, Folder 233)
    - Custom and Culture II: Black and white contact sheet and negatives. Images of corners, domes, arches and floors., 1979; cuid22322 (Box 2, Folder 234)
    - Custom and Culture II: black and white negatives and contact sheets. Images of buildings, stairs, buses., 1979; cuid22323 (Box 2, Folder 235)
    - Custom and Culture II: black and white negatives and contact sheets. Images of exterior ornamentation, interiors, pigeons., 1979; cuid22324 (Box 2, Folder 236)
    - Custom and Culture II: Black and white negatives and contact sheets. Images of trash cans, stairs, lighting fixtures, ironwork., 1979; cuid22325 (Box 2, Folder 237)
    - Custom and Culture II: Black and white contact sheet. Annotated. Images of fixtures, grates and doorways., 1979; cuid22326 (Box 2, Folder 238)
    - Custom and Culture II: Black and white contact sheet and negatives. Images of fixtures, grates and doorways., 1979; cuid22327 (Box 2, Folder 239)
    - Custom and Culture II: Black and white negatives and contact sheet. Images of books and windows., 1979; cuid22328 (Box 2, Folder 240)
    - Color snapshots and negatives. "Photo in pond by Customs House base of B'way. Photo for slide show. Shown at Fashion Moda" Images part of AC's "Animals Living in Cities" contribution., 1979; cuid22329 (Binder G, Folder a)
    - Andrea Callard and Mac Beckett in Milan. Color snapshots grouped in grey metal file box with two audiocassettes. Audiocassettes have been removed to Series ZZZZ: Media., 1979; cuid22330 (Binder G, Folder b)
    - Andrea Callard and Bonnie O'Neill's show at Site, Cite, Sight Inc. in San Francisco. Andrea Callard's file on her work "Commuting from Point to Point" a continuous slide show., 1980; cuid22331 (Box 2, Folder 241)
    - "Commuting from Point to Point" slideshow images., 1980; cuid22332 (Binder H, Folder a)
    - Color slides of Site, Cite, Sight exhibition space, location of Bonnie O'Neill and Andrea Callard show., 1980; cuid22333 (Binder H, Folder b)
    - Blue binder containing notecards, photographs and annotations. Used in Andrea Callard and Bonnie O'Neill's Site, Cite, Sight Inc. show., 1980; cuid22334 (Box 9, Folder 243)
    - Loose papers and photographs from the cover of blue binder, folder 243., 1980; cuid22335 (Box 2, Folder 244)
    - Matted color photographs from folder labeled "San Francisco". work from Site, Cite, Sight show., 1980; cuid22336 (Box 2, Folder 245)
    - Tanam Press publicitiy invitation for book release of "Hotel" and "Boiling Coffee" designed by Andrea Callard, 1980; cuid22337 (Box 2, Folder 246)
    - Flier used in an "effort to querry artists about [sewer?] conflict organized by White Columns", 1980; cuid22338 (Box 2, Folder 247)
    - Andrea Callard Show "Drawings in Series" at Ball State University in Muncie Indiana. Exhibition of pencil drawings AC made during the winter of 1973-1974., 1980; cuid22339 (Box 2, Folder 248)
    - Brooke Alexander Colab Benefit. Announcement and color slide of Andrea Callard's contribution., 1980; cuid22340 (Box 2, Folder 249)
    - Black and white photographs of fried eggs and plant leaves. Used in News and Nutrition work., 1980; cuid22341 (Box 2, Folder 254)
    - Andrea Callard Press, 1980; cuid22342 (Box 2, Folder 256)
    - Black and white negatives. Images of trash, Jeff Callard and Matthew Geller on the West Side highway at Chambers. Corresponding contact sheet in folder 260., 1980; cuid22343 (Box 2, Folder 259)
    - Black and white contact sheet. Images of Roberta Callard, Theresa Cha, Reese and Carol Williams., 1980; cuid22344 (Box 2, Folder 261)
    - Notebook, 1980-1981; cuid22345 (Box 2, Folder 262)
    - Color slides, 1980-1984. 21 slides on three pages., cuid22346 (Binder H, Folder c)
    - Color slides 1980-1984. 36 slides on three pages., cuid22347 (Binder H, Folder d)
    - Color slides 1980-1984. 45 slides on four pages., cuid22348 (Binder H, Folder e)
    - Color slides of show at White Columns. February 1981. 77 color slides., cuid22349 (Box 3, Folder 263)
    - "Whole more than two" Richard Miller and Andrea Callard Show at White Columns. 38 color slides, color negatives, publicity postcards, polaroids and notes., 1981; cuid22350 (Box 3, Folder 264)
    - White Columns Record Covers for Show. March 1981. 9 black and white slides, event announcements, Andrea Callard's exhibit contract and release form., cuid22351 (Box 3, Folder 266)
    - Black and white contact sheets. Images of recycling center in Western Massachusetts and the Cummington Community for the Arts., 1981; cuid22352 (Box 3, Folder 267)
    - Black and white negatives. Images of Cummington Community for the arts, Andrea Callard, Marjorie Cohen, Matthew Geller. Contact sheet in folder 269., 1981; cuid22353 (Box 3, Folder 268)
    - Black and white negatives. Images of Cummington Community for the Arts. Corresponding contact sheet in folder 271., 1981; cuid22354 (Box 3, Folder 270)
    - Black and white negatives. Images of Cummington Community for the Arts. Corresponding contact sheet in folder 273., 1981; cuid22355 (Box 3, Folder 272)
    - Color slides, Andrea Callard and Matthew Geller help move John Chamberlain from NYC to Florida. This trip was the inspiration for film ideas and watercolor paintings., 1981; cuid22356 (Box 3, Folder 276)
    - Index card notes, plans for film of trip to Florida with M. Geller., 1981; cuid22357 (Box 3, Folder 277)
    - Black and White contact sheet images of New York, Lispenard St, Carol and Reese Williams and Theresa Cha., 1981; cuid22358 (Box 3, Folder 278)
    - Black and white negatives. Indiana Farm. Includes negative used for AC's Colab Postcard "Braham Bull", 1981; cuid22359 (Box 3, Folder 279)
    - Black and white contact sheet and large print. Indiana Farm. Images of bulls., 1981; cuid22360 (Box 3, Folder 280)
    - Color Slides. Images of farm in Gaston Indiana.116 color slides, postcards, large black and white prints., 1981; cuid22361 (Box 3, Folder 281)
    - Folder labeled "Animals--Rupp" includes chicken sketches and a draft of a letter to the enditor written from Gaston Indiana., 1981; cuid22362 (Box 3, Folder 282)
  - Subseries E: 1982-1986
    - Art Works on Paper 1982-1991. 39 color slides on three pages, cuid22363 (Binder I, Folder a)
    - Art Works on Paper 1982-1991. 41 color slides on three pages., cuid22364 (Binder I, Folder b)
    - Art Works on Paper 1982-1991. 45 color slides on three pages, cuid22365 (Binder I, Folder c)
    - Art Works on Paper 1982-1991. 58 color slids on four pages., cuid22366 (Binder I, Folder d)
    - Bronx River Art Center "Inside/Out". Curated by Anne Philbin., 1983; cuid22367 (Box 3, Folder 287)
    - "Solid Signs of Geometry" sponsored by Creative Time. Performance piece., 1983; cuid22368 (Box 3, Folder 288)
    - Malone NY Residencey. 95 color slides: "Part of the time in Malone it was 14 belos. I saw amazing things and made lots of watercolors and drawings."0, 1983; cuid22369 (Box 3, Folder 289)
    - Chicago Books Picture Window announcement, 1983; cuid22370 (Box 3, Folder 290)
    - "Freckled Rice" Film directed by Stephen C. Ning, set design by Andrea Callard., 1983; cuid22371 (Box 3, Folder 291)
    - "Animal Life: Contemporary Representations" Benefit for the Animal Medical Center at Ericson Gallery., 1983; cuid22372 (Box 3, Folder 292)
    - Notebook. "Washington DC 200/ NYC", 1983; cuid22373 (Box 3, Folder 293)
    - Andrea Callard Press., 1983; cuid22374 (Box 3, Folder 294)
    - New American Landscape., 1983-1985; cuid22375 (Box 3, Folder 295)
    - Watercolor painted kimonos, 24 color slides, Color snapshots and polaroids., 1984; cuid22376 (Box 3, Folder 296)
    - Notebook. "Everglades", 1984; cuid22377 (Box 3, Folder 297)
    - Notebook "Black River/Buzzards/Etc.", 1984; cuid22378 (Box 3, Folder 298)
    - "Everglades City" by Matthew Geller. Editorial and Production consulting by Andrea Callard. Folder includes publicity and screening program., 1984; cuid22379 (Box 3, Folder 299)
    - Postcard of Andrea Callard's watercolor "Everglades City TV", 1984; cuid22380 (Box 3, Folder 300)
    - "Pus Factory" film file., 1984; cuid22381 (Box 3, Folder 301)
      Includes three eight inch floppy disks
    - Black and white negatives. Images of Ailanthus trees and an anti-nuclear demonstration. Corresponding contact sheets in folder 304., 1984; cuid22382 (Box 3, Folder 305)
    - Black and white negatives. Documentation of watercolors., 1984; cuid22383 (Box 3, Folder 306)
    - Andrea Callard Press., 1984; cuid22384 (Box 3, Folder 307)
    - Artworks on Paper 1984-1987. Catskill, Black River, Water, Iciles, Ice Dam. 35 color slides on three pages., cuid22385 (Binder I, Folder e)
    - Artworks on Paper 1984-1987. Catskill, Black River, Water, Iciles, Ice Dam. 41 color slides on three pages., cuid22386 (Binder I, Folder f)
    - Artworks on Paper 1984-1987. Catskill, Black River, Water, Iciles, Ice Dam. 30 color slides on three pages., cuid22387 (Binder I, Folder g)
    - Artworks on Paper 1984-1987. Catskill, Black River, Water, Iciles, Ice Dam. 61 color slides on four pages., cuid22388 (Binder I, Folder h)
    - Women in Jazz Downtown Poster. Rough layout., 1985; cuid22389 (Box 3, Folder 309)
    - New Prints from the Lexington Wake Up Printshop at Art Awareness. Works on paper and fabric. Includes Andrea Callard's work., 1985; cuid22390 (Box 3, Folder 310)
    - P.S. 1 Winter Opening. Includes Andrea Callard and Reese Williams's collaboration in the "Synaesthetics" portion. Postcard announcements, black and white negatives and contact sheets., 1985; cuid22391 (Box 3, Folder 311)
    - "Braham Bull" postcard. Andrea Callard's photograph contribution to "Greetings from NYC" Colab project., 1985; cuid22392 (Box 3, Folder 312)
    - "Today's Art in an Overpopulated Ctiy" at Exit Art. Includes Andrea Callard's work., 1986; cuid22393 (Box 3, Folder 313)
    - Andrea Callard Press, 1986, cuid22394 (Box 3, Folder 314)
  - Subseries F: 1987-1989
    - The Wake Up Printshop. press release, 1987; cuid22395 (Box 3, Folder 315)
    - Callard Press, 1987., cuid22396 (Box 3, Folder 317)
    - Chinatown History Project Tenement installation: Exhibition planning committee notes, 1987; cuid22397 (Box 3, Folder 318)
    - Chinatown Tenement installation: proposal description, ca. 1987; cuid22398 (Box 3, Folder 319)
    - Chinatown History Project Tenement Installation: Notes between Sam Sue and Andrea Callard., 1987-1988; cuid22399 (Box 3, Folder 320)
    - "The Tenement: Place for Survival, Object of Reform" publicity postcard. Installation curated by Sam Sue and Andrea Callard at the New York Chinatown History Project., 1988; cuid22400 (Box 3, Folder 321)
    - New York Chinatown History Project brochure, 1988; cuid22401 (Box 3, Folder 322)
    - Chinatown History Project walking tour., 1988; cuid22402 (Box 3, Folder 323)
    - Tenement Research, 1988; cuid22403 (Box 3, Folder 324)
    - Chinese and English wall calendar., 1988; cuid22404 (Box 3, Folder 325)
    - Tenement Project general schedual, 1988; cuid22405 (Box 3, Folder 326)
    - Tenement Installation: working drawings and lists., 1988; cuid22406 (Box 3, Folder 327)
    - Tenement Installation: exhibit floorplan., 1988; cuid22407 (Box 3, Folder 328)
    - Tenement Installation: Andrea Callard's notes, 1988; cuid22408 (Box 3, Folder 329)
    - Tenement installation: descriptive note, 1988; cuid22409 (Box 3, Folder 330)
    - Tenement Installation: exhibition script, 1988; cuid22410 (Box 3, Folder 331)